Guide to the Brooklyn Arts Council Folk Arts collection CBHM.0002
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 2: Black Brooklyn Renaissance
  - Sub-series 2.1: Program Files
    - Lincoln Center Out of Doors, The Robert Glasper Experiment, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Otto Neals and Emmett Wigglesworth, Exhibition, BAC Gallery, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Amateur Night at the Apollo: Brooklyn Night, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Dance Kings of Black Brooklyn, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Carnival Masquerades (Exhibition), 2010 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - The Black Brooklyn Renaissance Conference and Concert, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Brooklyn: The Gospel Borough, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Word is Brooklyn, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - The Brooklyn School of Black Visual Artists, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Intergenerations: Randy Weston Trio with Ayanda Clarke, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Voices of the Elders, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Apollo Concert, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - BBR Finale, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Contact Sheets, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Community Interviews Scheduled, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Community Interviews, Possible Interviewees, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Interview Notes and Emails, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Permissions, Denied or Restricted, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Permissions, A-B, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Permissions, C-F, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Permissions, G-J, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Permissions, K-M, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Permissions, N-S, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Permissions, T-Z, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Baba Lee Abramson, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Afro-Mosiac Soul, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Harold Akyeampong, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Jean Alexander, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Tai Allen, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Asase Yaa, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Frisner Augustin, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Stephanie Battle, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Anthony Bonair, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Nathaniel Hakika Boyd, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn Jumbies, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Camille A. Brown, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Ron Brown, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Glenda Cadogan, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Lizz Carr, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Dolores Carty, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Ayanda Clarke, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Neil Clarke, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Nora Chipaumire, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Climbing Poetree, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Sewaa Codrington, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Conjunto Nuevo Milenio, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Coole High, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - D-Cross, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Laurie Cumbo, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Olu Dara, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Rev Herbert Daughtry, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - George Davidson, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Marcelle Davies-Lashley, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Kevin "Fuzzy" Davis, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Mickey Davis, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Vado Diomande, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Ray "Chino" Diaz, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Brian "Dyalekt" Kushner, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Ogundipe Fayomi, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Jamel Gaines, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Izell Glover, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Ronnie Goodwin, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Doris Green, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Talu Green, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Brenda Greene, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Gaylord Hassan, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Kathy Hernandez, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Kid Lucky, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - LMNOP aka Lesliayn, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Keith Wonderboy Johnson, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Sonya Johnson, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - MT Kalla Keaton, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Youssouf Koumbassa, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Michela Lerman, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - James Lovell, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - John Mason, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Karl McIntosh, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Sarah McLawler, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Michael Manswell, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Cal Massey, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Alfredo Mighty, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Charlotte Mishell, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Ella Moore, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Baba Mpho, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Bob Myers, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Ngoma, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Ademola Olugebefola, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Jose Ortiz, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Pegasus Rising, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Sam Pinn, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Montague Pollard, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Montague Pollard, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Obara Wali Rahman, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Toshi Reagon, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Tony Reece, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Kenya Robinson, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - SagaOne, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Abdel Salaam, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Roger "Montego Joe" Sanders, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Segun Shabaka, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Shock-A-Lock, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Danny Simmons, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - S.W.A.T., 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Les Slater, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Alex Smith Jr., 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Enoch Smith Jr., 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Pamela Sneed, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Baraka de Soleil, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Somi, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Nepo Soteri, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Tah Phrum Duh Bush, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - DJ Tahleim, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Greg Tate, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - M-TRI, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Austin Tuitt, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Edwina Tyler, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Hanifah / Walidah, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Junior Wedderburn, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Randy Weston, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Reffie Wilson, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Obediah Wright, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Tantra Zawadi, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Jawole Willa Joe Zollar, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - 227 Abolitionist Place, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Abrahams, Roger D, "Black Talking on the Streets," Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - African American Burial Ground Project, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - African Diaspora, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Black Academics, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Black Neighborhoods, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Afro Renaissance, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Caribbean Carnival, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Dance, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - International African Street Festival, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Jazz, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Literature, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Music, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - People of the Sun Middle Passage Collective, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Theater, Research, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Art, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Arts Festivals, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Caribbean Culture, Context, 2009-2011 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Dance, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Drill Teams, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Fashion, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Film, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jazz, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Misc., 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Music, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Neighborhoods, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Photography, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Theater, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - West Indian Carnival, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Women, Context, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Sub-series 2.2: Audiovisual
    Events represented in the Audiovisal sub-series:
    Hip Hop Hybrids of Brooklyn. Public assembly, 70 North 6th Street, Williamsburg. Presented by BAC with support from American Express, April 15, 2010.
    Hip Hop Hybrids of Brooklyn. Public assembly, 70 North 6th Street, Williamsburg. Presented by BAC with support from American Express, May 22, 2010.
    Intergenerations: Toshi Reagon and Friends. Southpaw, 125 Fifth Aavenue. Presented by BAC with support from American Express and Emma A. Shaefer Charitable Turst, July 29, 2010.
    Otto Neals and Emmett Wigglesworth: Kindred Spirits Forging Forward. Exhibition in the BAC gallery, September 24, 2010-January 4, 2011.
    Word is Brooklyn. BAM Café, presented by BAC in cooperation with City Lore, November 19, 2010.
    Voices of the Elders. Reception, interviews and panel discussion. Long Island University. Presented by BAC in cooperation with Ifetayo Cultural Arts Academy, January 30, 2011.
    Black Brooklyn Renaissance: The New Generation. Project finale, BAMcafé, co-presented by BAC and BAMcafe live, February 11-12, 2011.
    Interviews include:
    Frisner Augustin, undated
    Dolores Carty, Fulton Art Fair, 4/27/2011
    Francina Connors, 5/13/2011
    Olu Dara, 5/9/2011
    Herbert Daughtry, 4/13/2011
    Jeff King, 5/6/2010
    Novella Nelson, 5/9/2011
    Donald Sangster, undated
    Charles Tolliver, 5/15/2011
    Reggie Workman, 5/5/2011
    Other individual interviews are listed below by category.
    - African Dance / Brooklyn Style BCBC, 2010 (Box 32, Disk 1-23)
    - Rites and Ceremonies of the Brooklyn African Diaspora, 2010 (Box 32, Disk 24-35)
    - Icons of Brooklyn Jazz, 2010 (Box 32, Disk 36-46)
    - Hip Hop Hybrids of Brooklyn, 2010 (Box 32, Disk 47-62)
    - BAM DanceAfrica, Pre-Opening Activities, 2010 (Box 32, Disk 63-76)
    - Black Brooklyn Drum Call, 2010 (Box 32, Disk 77-96)
    - 21st Annual Tribute to Our Ancestors of the Middle Passage, 2010 (Box 33, Disk 1-25)
    - Preserving the Parade: Documenting the West Indian American Labor Day Carnival, 2010 (Box 33, Disk 26-40)
    - Intergenerations: Toshi Regon and Friends, 2010 (Box 33, Disk 41-51)
    - J'ouvert West Indian Labor Day Parade, 2010 (Box 33, Disk 52-54)
    - BAC Gallery Public Program. Emmett Wigglesworth Storytelling, 2010 (Box 33, Disk 55-56)
    - Intergenerations: Dance Kings of Black Brooklyn, 2010 (Box 33, Disk 57-66)
    - Black Brooklyn Renaissance Conference and Concert, 2010 (Box 33, Disk 67-124)
    - Brooklyn: The Gospel Borough, 2010 (Box 34, Disk 1-8)
    - Word is Brooklyn, 2010 (Box 34, Disk 9-17)
    - The Brooklyn School of Black Visual Arts, 2010 (Box 34, Disk 18-27)
    - Intergenerations: Randy Weston Trio With Special Guest Ayanda, 2010 (Box 34, Disk 28-30)
    - Voices of the Elders, 2011 (Box 34, Disk 31-42)
    - Amateur Night at the Apollo: Brooklyn Night, 2011 (Box 34, Disk 43-49)
    - BBR: The New Generation, 2011 (Box 34, Disk 50-62)
    - Interviews: Program Interviews, 2010-2011 (Box 34, Disk 63-83)
      - Hip Hop Hybrids, 2010 April 15
        Dyalekt, Ngoma, Charlotte Mishell, DJ Leecy T and M-TRI, D. Cross, Isaac, Coole High, Tantra Zawadi
      - Drum Call, 2010 June 5
        Jose Ortiz, The Kutters (Tony Reece), Austin Tuit, Harold Akyeampong, Junior "Gabu" Wedderburn
      - Toshi Reagon and Friends, 2010 July 29
        Stephanie Battle, DJ Shay, Jose James
      - Voices of the Elders, 2011 January 30
        Beryl Quamie, Chuck Fowler, Gloria Pickering, Harold Valle, Selma Jackson
      - Black Brooklyn Renaissance, 2011 May 9
        Climbing Poetree
      - Black Brooklyn Renaissance: The New Generation, 2011 February 11
    - Interviews: Individual, Community Interviews, 2010 (Box 34, Disk 84-108)
      - Yejkle Akinlana, 2010 October 7
      - Maxine Alexander, 2010 November 11
      - Leslie Arlette-Boyce, 2010 July 27
      - Millie Burns, 2010 December 14
      - Elizabeth Carr, 2010 September 21
      - Fikisha Cumbo, 2010 February 13
      - Susan Goldbetter, 2010 July 27
      - Velma Johnson, 2010 December 13
      - Jeffrey Perry, 2010 November 8
      - Joanna Petit-Frere, 2010 March 16
      - Nepo Soteri, 2010 July 23
      - Austin Tuit and Nana O, 2010 March 17
    - Interviews: Individual, Community Arts Organizations, 2010-2011 (Box 34, Disk 109-117)
      - Peggy Alston, 2010 July 27
      - Safiya Bandele, 2010 December 13
      - Hakika Boyd, 2010 November 8
      - Gaylord Hassan, 2010 March 16
      - Bob Myers, 2010 July 23
      - Les Slater, 2010 March 17
    - Interviews: Individual, Community Festival / Ritual Arts, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 1-10)
      - Jean Alexander, 2011 April 4
      - Glenda Cadogan, 2011 February 14
      - Kevin "Fuzzy" Davis, 2011 April 6
      - Kathyann Hernandez, 2011 March 18
        Interviewed by Kay Turner.
      - Baba Mpho, 2010 August 6
      - Segun Shabaka, 2010 October 25
      - John Mason, 2010 November 20
    - Interviews: Individual, Dance, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 11-33)
      - Rahkiah Abdurahman, undated
      - Kyle Abraham, 2011 March 23
      - Calvin Booker, 2011 January 7
      - Ron Brown, 2010 March 23
      - Nora Chipaumire, 2010 July 23
      - Sewaa Codrington, 2011 March 14
      - Mickey Davidson, 2011 February 16
      - Jamal Gaines, 2010 December 27
        Interviewed by Nicole Macotsis.
      - Doris Green, 2010 July 30
      - Youssouf Koumbassa, 2011 March 22
      - Michela Marino Lerman, 2011 March 22
      - Michael Manswell, 2010 July 27
        Interviewed by AB.
      - Ella Thompson Moore, 2011 April 22
      - Francine Ott, 2011 February 4
      - Walter Rutledge, 2011 April 8
      - Baraka de Soleil, 2011 February 2
      - Nathan Trice, 2011 April 8
      - Reggie Wilson, undated
      - Obediah Wright, 2011 January 10
      - Jawole Willa Jo Zollar, 2011 March 10
    - Interviews: Individual, Gospel, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 34-36)
      - Phil Groves, 2011 March 15
      - Keith "Wonderboy" Johnson, 2010 November 4
      - Team T-N-T, 2010 October 19
    - Interviews: Individual, Hip Hop, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 37-42)
      - Demostina, 2011 February 11
      - Dyalekt, 2011 February 11
      - Ngoma, 2010 October 26
      - Tah Phrum Duh Bush, 2010 March 5
    - Interviews, Individual, Jazz, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 43-58)
      - Ahmed Abdullah, 2010 May 18
      - Cecil Bridgewater, 2010 May 18
      - Sarah McLawler, 2011
      - Sam Pinn, 2011 April 5
      - Somi, 2010 May 15
      - Jitu Weusi, 2011 May 6
    - Interviews: Individual, Literature, 2011 (Box 35, Disk 59)
      One interview with Brenda Greene, February 2, 2011.
    - Interviews: Individual, Percussion, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 60-71)
      - Baba Lee Abramson, 2010 July 25
      - Harold Akyeampong, 2010 August 26
      - Ayanda Clarke, 2011 March 10
      - Ray "Chino" Diaz, 2010 July 21
      - LaTroupe Makandel, 2010 July 20
      - Montego Joe, 2010 June 11
      - Monty Pollard, 2010 July 16
      - Obara Wali Rahman, 2011 February 16
      - Tony Reece, 2010 February 19
      - Edwina Tyler, 2010 July 19
    - Interviews: Individual, Pop, 2011 (Box 35, Disk 72-77)
      - Alsarah, 2011 April 8
      - Stephanie Battle, 2011 April 29
      - Marcelle Davies-Lashley, 2011 February 24
      - Ronnie Goodman, 2011 April 5
      - Toshi Reagon, 2011 May 11
      - Sun Singleton, 2011 April 7
    - Interviews: Individual, Spoken Word, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 78-87)
      - Tai Allen, 2011 March 17
      - Climbing Poetree, 2011 May 9
      - George Davidson, 2010 November 2
      - Tammy Hall, 2011 March 16
      - James Lovell, 2010 July 28
      - Tuan X, 2011 February 1
      - Hanifah Walidah, 2011 March 25
    - Interviews: Individual, Theater, 2011 (Box 35, Disk 88-90)
      - Josephine English, 2011 April 8
      - Bernard Marsh, 2011 February 21
      - E.W. McDonald, 2011 February 15
    - Interviews: Individual, Visual Art, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 91-101)
      - Anthony Bonair, 2010 July 23
      - Laurie Cumbo, 2011 March 29
      - Ogundipe Fayomi, 2011 March 15
      - Izell Glover, 2011 February 18
      - LeRoy Henderson, 2011 February 16
      - Kenya (Robinson), 2011 January 4
      - Karl McIntosh, 2011 January 4
      - Alfredo Mighty, 2011 April 11
      - Otto Neals, 2011 January 20
      - Ademola Olugebefola, 2011 March 10
      - Danny Simmons, 2011 April 26
      - Emmett Wigglesworth, 2010 July 12
    - Interviews: Extra Copies, 2010-2011 (Box 35, Disk 102-116)
    - Interviews, Individual, Not Categorized, 2010-2011 (Box 36, Disk 1-25)
    - Related Media, 2010-2011 (Box 36, Disk 26-32)
    - Black Brooklyn Renaissance Archive for Library of Congress, 2010-2011 (Box 37)
      32 original Hi8 tapes and 1 thumb drive. Inventory included in box.
- Series 3: Brooklyn Maqam Arab Music Festival
  The Brooklyn Maqam Arab Music Festival was a celebration of Arab music traditions in Brooklyn held March 2-30, 2008. The Arabic word "maqam" refers to a group of musical notes and patterns of notes that form the building blocks of traditional Arab music. There are dozens of different maqamat, each of which creates its own characteristic sound and mood. BAC's Brooklyn Maqam included of a series of concerts, symposia, and workshops featuring nearly 100 New York-based musicians and groups representing musical traditions from Egypt, Yemen, Palestine, Iraq, Morocco, Syria and Lebanon. Musical programs included popular contemporary arrangements, folk traditions (both well-known and rare) and fusion pieces that integrate old and new styles. All events were open to the public free of charge. Brooklyn Arts Council staff involved in this project were Kay Turner, Folk Arts Director and Nicole Macotsis, Folk Arts Associate.
  Program Files include research materials, interviews, event documentation, publicity materials, documentation of funding efforts, and budgets for the project. The Audiovisual sub-series includes audio and video tapes of artists considered and accepted for participation in the events and digital photographs.
  Featured artists:
  Simon Shaheen (Palestinian oud and violin)
  Tareq Abboushi (Palestinian buzuq player)
  Ahmed Alrodini (Yemeni singer, percussionist and oud player)
  Yoel Ben-Simhon (composer, vocalist and instrumentalist of Israeli and Moroccan descent)
  Amir ElSaffar (Iraqi-American santoor player specializing in Iraqi Maqam)
  Gaida Hinnawi (Syrian vocalist)
  Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak (Brooklyn's Syrian-American band leader)
  Naji Youssef (Lebanese Cantor for the Catholic Melkite Church)
  Shoshana Tubi (specialist in Yemeni wedding songs)
  Due to sensitive personal information, materials in box 100, folder 4 are not open for research.
  - Sub-series 3.1: Program Files
    - Research, Arab Culture, Web Sources, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Research, Arab Music, Articles and Liner Notes, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Research, Arab Music, Web Sources, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Research, Consultants, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Research, Contacts, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Research, Partners and Venues, Printed Matter, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Related Events and Organizations, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Similar Events, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Kay Turner, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Nicole Macotsis, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Nicole Macotsis, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Letters of Intent, Artists, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Letters of Intent, Venues, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Interviews, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Events, BAM Cafe, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Roundtable: Arab Music Traditions and Their History in Brooklyn, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Voice of the Women, Kingsborough Community College, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Timeless Traditions from Egypt and Iraq, Joe's Pub, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Cultural Walking Tours, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Flyers, Programs, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Oversize Posters, BAC Newsletter Promotional, 2008 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Program Drafts and Notes, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Programming and Scheduling Notes, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Fact Sheet, Schedule, Talking Points, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Banners, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Arabs in the Press/Media, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Arab Media, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - General Media, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Notes, Nicole Macotsis, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Sheet Flyer, Arabic, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Street Flyer, English, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Budgets, FY 2008 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Funders Credits, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Funding, American Express, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Funding, Mary Duke Biddle Foundation, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Funding, Elebash Fund, JP Morgan Chase, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Funding, National Endowment for the Arts, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Funding, New York State Music Fund Application, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Funding, New York State Music Fund, Reports, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Budget, General, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Budget, Artist Fees and Receipts, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Check Requests and Contracts, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Contracts and Receipts, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Contracts, RESTRICTED, 2008 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Design and Film Editing, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, Correspondence, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Performers, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Performers, Eddie "The Shick" Kochack, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Sub-series 3.2: Audiovisual
    Interviews and events represented in the Audiovisual sub-series:
    Cassettes:
    Yasser Khalifa interviewed by Kay Turner and Nicole Macotsis, May 24, 2005
    Mohamed Bechar, part 2 of 2, interviewed by Nicole Macotsis, August 23, 2005
    Tareq Abboushi interviewed by Kate Turner and Nicole Macotsis, May 10, 2006
    Gaida Hinnawi interviewed by Kay Turner, July 30, 2007
    Galeet Dardashti interviewed by Kay Turner and Nicole Macotsis, August 28, 2007
    Malika Zarra interviewed by Kay Turner and Nicole Macotsis, September 12, 2007
    CDs:
    Track 1: Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak, interviewed by Nicole Macotsis, August 23, 2006; Track 2, Gamal Shafik interviwed by Kay Turner and Nicole Macotsis, November 13, 2007
    Track 3: Amir ElSaffar
    Track 4: Youssef Kassab interviewed by Nicole Macotsis, November 19, 2007; Track 5: Youssef Kassab, part 2 of 2, interviewed by Nicole Macotsis, November 19, 2007
    Events by location:
    Alwan, March 29, 2008, (5 CDs total recording 3 sets; track lists; one CD is a rough cut video)
    Brooklyn Public Library (2 CDs recording 3 sets, track list)
    Kingsborough, March 16, 2008 (6 CDs recording 3 sets, track lists)
    Lafayette Grill, Arab-o-Rama, March 14, 2008 (1 CD)
    Najeeb's, March 14, 2008 (2 CDs, track lists)
    The mini-DVDs document Brooklyn Maqam performances as follows:
    Karim Nagi, March 6, 2008, 2 mini-DVDs
    Arab-o-Rama, March 14, 2008, Cedars/IBIS